{
    "subject": "resource/Qt_Project",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Qt_(framework)",
    "human_readable": "Qt Project is about Category:Qt_(framework).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7651079297065735,
            "question": "What type of software development framework is Qt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731350302696228,
            "question": "What are some of the key features of the Qt framework?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6823633313179016,
            "question": "What is the Qt Project primarily focused on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4872637987136841,
            "question": "Does the Qt Project offer tools for designing user interfaces?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46429720520973206,
            "question": "What companies or organizations widely utilize Qt for development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44732147455215454,
            "question": "Is Qt primarily used for web development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4290704131126404,
            "question": "Are there any popular open-source applications built using Qt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3738524615764618,
            "question": "What programming languages are supported by Qt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.368927925825119,
            "question": "What platforms can applications built with Qt be deployed to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3588957190513611,
            "question": "Can Qt be used to create cross-platform applications?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Qt Project is about Category:Qt_(framework).",
            "html": "dbpedia_5008_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What platforms can applications built with Qt be deployed to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5008_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What programming languages are supported by Qt?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5008_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular open-source applications built using Qt?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5008_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5008_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided discuss various aspects of the Qt framework, confirming that it is indeed a project focused on developing cross-platform applications. The information in the documents supports the statement that Qt Project is about Category:Qt_(framework)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}